<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shubham Sharma</title>
    <description>A Personal Website for sharing thoughts and ideas about Technology.
</description>
    <link>http://shubhamsharma.in/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://shubhamsharma.in/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 18:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 18:48:31 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to my new website!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my first blog post!. I am very excited for this blog, so much so that a few exclamation marks cannot communicate the excitement, so here are a few emoticons :-D :-D :-P.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, coming back to the point of this article, which is to give a nice direction to this blog and mark a milestone for me.
In the near future this blog will be focused mostly on Technical stuff like, playing with new frameworks, providing how-tos for fellow learners and just generally writing about life of a programmer which revolves around these technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a geek I try out new things quite often, so most of the time I loose track of what I have previously tested and played with. So, Hopefully this blog will be like a book keeping tool for all the technologies I have played with in the past and a constant reminder to try out something new and keep things nice and interesting for someone who might accidentally stumble upon this website :-).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS:- As you can see from the structure of the post that I am a newbie at writing posts, so please bare with me :-). I intend to learn as I write more posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 03:49:28 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://shubhamsharma.in/new/website/2015/04/16/welcome-to-my-new-website.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://shubhamsharma.in/new/website/2015/04/16/welcome-to-my-new-website.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>new</category>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
